this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
in an effort to save his brother ace who had been captured by the navy
luffy journeys to the great prison known as impel down meanwhile the other straw hats scattered
around the globe by bartholomew kuma face struggles of their own the friends whereabouts an island of
giant birds and a pink paradise
how many times must i repeat myself
are my instructions too complicated to penetrate that thick head of yours
i require at least 100 kilos of food per meal anything less than that is completely insufficient
do you want to be turned to stone again no please we're very sorry we'll be more careful next time
bring her another meal to her specifications to replace this one
here you are luffy open wide for me okay
simply delectable and when you're the one feeding it to me why it makes it all the sweeter
oh go on
clearly that's exactly what he would say
what are you doing over there who are you talking to
aren't you gonna eat something
the sea king hands unbelievable
no no it's fine please help yourself
i'm more than satisfied just as i am
damn it i can't see anything
i know the curtain's closed
hold on a minute there's an open space right over here
oh
Blue?
Wolfie, guys?
Why isn't anybody else here?
Did they kill them?
That's ridiculous, don't even think it!
It's not true, it can't be!
Guys!
It goes, it's really klassy-
Hey, Chopper!
Lufie!
You're here!
When I woke up and I was all alone, I wasn't scared at all.
Really?
Fuse up, come on.
Knock it off.
Stop, you big dummy.
You guys are going to regret this.
You hear me?
Hey, where the heck did these birds come from?
They're huge!
Don't even think about trying to eat me!
No, my body's too stiff to get up and run.
I gotta move!
Oh!
Don't leave me alone!
Oh, I'm scared!
It's great!
I'm scared!
Oh!
Hmm?
No! Let me go!
Bastard!
Huh?
Uh...
This island is weird!
This is a dream, right?
Please let it be a dream!
I wanna wake up!
No, it's gonna hurt!
No, you birds are mean!
I'm a reindeer, not a toy!
Yeah!
No, it's gonna hurt!
I'm a reindeer, not a toy!
Why?
No, it's gonna hurt!
I'm a reindeer!
Oh, it's gonna hurt!
No, it's gonna hurt my heart
Yeah!
But then you're ready to break the world!
Huh?
I don't know what the world is!
Huh...
Huh?
There aren't any people here
Just birds
Hey, Luffy
Everybody
I'm the only one on this island
What am I going to do?
I'm so thirsty
And hungry, too
If only Luffy and the others were here
Even on a deserted island
They'd still throw an awesome party
A party
Who am I kidding?
I'm lost and they could be dead for all I know
I can't take it!
Where is everybody?
Guys!
Luffy!
Oh, yeah!
This!
We promised that no matter what happened
We'd meet up wherever this fever card leads us
Luffy and the others will be waiting
I just know it!
Nothing can stop them!
They won't ever give up!
And that goes for me, too
This is no time to sit around and do nothing
That's why I gotta eat and get stronger
This fruit is pretty bitter, though
But I need nutrients
This one is super sour
Gotcha!
I'll need me to survive, too
This guy doesn't look too yummy, though, I guess
But what can you expect on an island like this?
Gotta make do
Whoa!
You come back here, dinner!
Can't get away from me!
Huh?
Uh
What the?
I wonder who the heck hit me
Ow!
Uh
Why is it so hot?
I was supposed to catch dinner, not be it
It's rare to get raccoon on an island
Raccoon hot pot
Raccoon nice
But me rather have chicken and make chicken hot pot
That good idea, but no chicken
Raccoon will have to do for now
Stop it!
Shut up!
I'm a reindeer!
Huh?
Ah, guess we have reindeer hot pot then
Hey, wait!
Did reindeer just say something?
Me not know rangers could speak
God, you're finally listening!
Now let me down!
Dad!
We got prices on hands!
We tried to sneak up into bird's nest!
But bird caught us!
I know, but you birds are coming right for us.
Maybe we could shoo away.
Me say we run for it.
We go now.
Come on, guys.
Don't leave your reindeer hop-hop behind for the birds.
Those birds are really strong, huh?
Oh, crap.
The birds rolled me around like a toy,
and those humans tried to eat me in a hot pot.
What the hell's wrong with this crazy island?
This island is known as Birdie Kingdom,
a place where birds reign supreme.
One legend suggests that its lands are filled with hidden treasure,
but all Chopper has found his danger.
Behold, Peachy Island,
a dreamy, beautiful destination on the Grand Line.
My dearest Nami,
my sweet Robin.
It's been a while.
How are the two of you doing?
As for me, I'm...
Where the hell am I?
Bastard.
This is all because of that damn warlord.
Oh, my goodness.
Excuse me.
Mister, are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Please, say something.
Anything.
I can feel a tender touch.
I smell something sweet.
I'm in the lap of a beautiful woman.
Is it Nami?
Maybe Robin.
No, I must be dreaming.
It doesn't matter.
All I know is I want to stay here forever.
Hey, wait a minute.
Come back!
What's this?
You forgot your handkerchief!
I guess it wasn't a dream.
Elizabeth.
I still don't have a clue where I'm at.
Beautiful.
Maybe I ended up in heaven.
Her name is Elizabeth.
If this place really is heaven, then is she an angel?
Oh, my heart is pounding.
What is this feeling so warm?
This must be love.
I sense romance in the air.
No, I can't think about such things right now.
Nami and Robin are out there waiting for me.
But, well, the least I can do is think of her kindness.
Through thick and thin, a gentleman must always be courteous to a lady!
Oh, baby, Robin!
Please forgive me for being unfaithful!
Elizabeth!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's the same design as the handkerchief.
Then this must be Elizabeth's place, I presume?
Hello, Lady Elizabeth!
My name's Sanji.
You were looking after me not too long ago.
I came here to return your handkerchief.
Hey, you didn't give me a chance to say thanks!
Nope, hold on.
Shouldn't rush it.
She's obviously a shy and innocent girl.
I need to be cool.
Have a little patience.
Pardon my manners.
Didn't mean to be rude.
Your hand was...
It was so lovely, I couldn't help myself.
I just wanted to think his beautiful owner face to face.
But here I am being too forward again.
Perhaps you would allow me to apologize and say thanks as well
by giving me the honor of cooking for you.
Whatever you'd like, I'll make it.
Believe it or not, I'm a world-class chef.
Or not.
So you...
You really like to cook?
Oh, yes!
I love cooking!
Then do you like clothes, too?
Clothes?
Like fashion?
Yeah!
Unlike some stupid swordsman I know,
I actually care a lot about the way I look.
Really?
You're not just saying that.
Oh, no!
Then what about dresses?
Dresses?
Uh...
Oh, I get it!
She keeps asking me about stuff like that
because she wants to know what I'm into!
She's making a love connection!
What do you think of dresses like this?
Like them?
I love them!
They're beautiful!
Oh, you have no idea how much!
And what about flower prints?
Hell yes!
Nothing in life beats a gorgeous flower print!
Oh, they're so adorable!
All right, then!
Finally!
Sweet Elizabeth is opening up to me after all!
Oh, you have exquisite taste, my dear!
Don't be shy!
You've already opened the door to your home!
Now open the door to your heart!
Oh, Sanji!
No need to hold anything back, my love!
Just leap into my arms!
Oh, Elizabeth!
I think this dress would look amazing on you!
Ouch!
Wasn't ready for that!
You're a lot stronger than I thought you would be,
my dear Elizabeth!
No!
I was right!
I must be dreaming after all!
I'll be dreaming after all!
But this is a nightmare!
We like the same things! That makes you one of us!
This is a safe place!
You don't have to pretend to be something you're not anymore!
Yes! It's a free country where you can be yourself!
Now, put on this dress and open up the door to your heart!
No! I'm not gonna open anything!
This island is known as the Second Maiden Island.
Everything here is pink.
All of the animals and people who come to this land share a common bond.
No matter what forms their bodies take, they still have girlish hearts.
Robin, I think this was heaven!
Robin, come back here!
Leave me alone, you weirdos! I already told you I'm not into that kind of crap!
My dearest Nami, my sweet Robin, it's been a while. How are the two of you doing?
As for me, I'm...
Well, uh...
How to put this...
Don't run, sugar!
You can't fight it!
You're one of us now!
Oh yeah, fat chance!
Welcome to Kamabaka Kingdom!
No, it's obvious.
I'm in hell!
The End
Raman finds herself in a faraway land with inhabitants that have been forced to work for 700 years, day and night.
She must either help them or become enslaved herself.
Meanwhile, Usopp awakens in a land full of mysterious and deadly plant life.
On the next Wood Piece, The Friends' Whereabouts, bridging the islands and vicious vegetation, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!